JULIAN TIMBS

DETAILS

ADDRESS

Brisbane Australia

PHONE

0405549229

EMAIL

timbsjulian@gmail.com

SKILLS

Fast Learner

Ability to Work in a Team

Communication Skills

Decision Making Skills

Complex Problem Solving

PROFILE

Dedicated worker with 1.5 years experience in sales in various industries and 3 months experience in 360 recruitment. Experience with phone based sales and customer service and support, as well as, sourcing, cold calling and interviewing. Enjoy working in a team and interacting with customers.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Inbound Consumer Sales, TSA Group

Brisbane

May 2023

Working within the Telstra inbound consumer sales department. Tasked with service and sales responsibilities including transitioning from service to sales. Experience with multiple systems such as Salesforce and interacting with a broad customer base.

Recruitment Consultant, Optimum Consulting

Jan 2023 — Mar 2023

Involved in 360 recruitment including sourcing, interviewing, shortlisting and being client facing. Specialising in recruitment of technical services which encompassed the engineering, mining, ESG fields among others.

Salesperson, Haymans

Brisbane

Jan 2022 — Jan 2023

Fully autonomous position which involves working with solar installers to ensure they could get their solar systems to their warehouse or to site Australia wide. This would include finding stock, logistics, planning, teamwork and communication. Phone based customer service with solar installers to ensure they could solve product issues and find solutions for their jobs.

Storeperson, Haymans

Brisbane

Jul 2021 — Jan 2022

Worked as a picker and in receiving at an electrical wholesale warehouse. Picking involved attention to detail, quality assurance involving assessment of the quality of an individual item and also the state of the packaging. Working in receiving involved receipting inbound inventory, quality assurance and inventory management.

EDUCATION

HSC, Nudgee College

Brisbane

Nov 2019

Graduated high school with an OP of 9

REFERENCES

References available upon request